* Login
* Sign Up

Privacy Statement
=================

Privacy statement
-----------------

Intuitive Password operates several websites including IntuitivePassword.com. It is Intuitive Password's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. Below is our privacy statement which incorporates these goals: (1) We don't allow you to send any critically important information such as your sensitive data, login password and Master Password to any person including our employees. (2) We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (3) We don't share or sale your personal information including your email address with anyone except to comply with the law or protect our rights.

Website visitors
----------------

Like most website operators, Intuitive Password collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Intuitive Password's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Intuitive Password's visitors use its website. From time to time, Intuitive Password may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Intuitive Password also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Intuitive Password does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

Gathering of personally identifying information
-----------------------------------------------

Certain visitors to Intuitive Password's websites choose to interact with Intuitive Password in ways that require Intuitive Password to gather personally identifying information. The amount and type of information that Intuitive Password gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at IntuitivePassword.com to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with Intuitive Password are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Intuitive Password collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Intuitive Password. Intuitive Password does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website related activities.

Use of personal data
--------------------

Intuitive Password may collect aggregated statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Intuitive Password may monitor the most popular website account on the IntuitivePassword.com site. Intuitive Password may display this information publicly or provide it to others. In addition, Intuitive Password may use your behavioral data and other data you provide to Intuitive Password to customize advertisements on its site to its users. In this way we try to keep the majority of our services free. However, Intuitive Password does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of certain personally identifying information
--------------------------------------------------------

Intuitive Password discloses potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Intuitive Password's behalf or to provide services available at Intuitive Password's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Intuitive Password's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Intuitive Password will not rent or sell potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Intuitive Password discloses potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Intuitive Password believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Intuitive Password, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Intuitive Password website and have supplied your email address, Intuitive Password may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Intuitive Password and our products. We expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Intuitive Password takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information.

Cookies
-------

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Intuitive Password uses cookies to help Intuitive Password identify and track visitors, their usage of Intuitive Password website, and their website access preferences. Intuitive Password visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Intuitive Password' websites, with the drawback that certain features of Intuitive Password's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Changes to privacy statement
----------------------------

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Intuitive Password may change its Privacy Statement from time to time, and in Intuitive Password's sole discretion. Intuitive Password encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Statement.

[Login](https://www.intuitivepassword.com/en/Account/AccountLogin) English Deutsch Español Français Italiano Português Pусский Română 日本語 한국어 简体中文 繁體中文

#### Products

#### Resources

#### Tools

#### Company

* Contact Us

* Location
    
    542 Station Street  
    Box Hill, VIC 3128, Australia

#### Ask a Question

Send

* * *

© 2013-2024 Intuitive Security Systems Pty. Ltd.  
ABN 22 168 534 156. Software Made in Australia.
